1automationwiz.com 2018-08-21

# 1AutomationWiz.com Privacy Policy

**Stated Purpose** :  

1AutomationWiz.com., a Delaware corporation, DBA Cyber Samurai Marketing, inc, having its principal address of business at 11939 Manchester Rd., STE: 198, St. Louis, MO 63131, USA (“we”, “us” or “our”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) together with our End User Licence and any other documents referred to therein sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting any of our 1AutomationWiz.com websites (“Site”) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

For the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (the “GDPR”),Web.com Group Inc., located at 12808 Gran Bay Parkway West, Jacksonville, FL 32258. is the data processor for 1AutomationWiz.com.

**Information we may collect about you** :

We may collect and process the following data about you,

**Information you give us:**

_Contact information._  We collect and retain personal contact information that you submit to us voluntarily in signing up to use our products and services or any mailing lists. This may include any or all of the following: your name, mailing address, web address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address. Additionally, we collect contact information provided to us during any correspondence relating to customer support, as well as in connection with products and services offered on our Sites.

_Financial Information_. We collect and retain financial information you provide when you order our products and services. For example, when you sign up for any of our products or services through 1AutomationWiz.com, we require you to provide a credit card number and billing address before we process that application.  

_Information on your use of the Site.  _We collect information about the device with which your use to access our Sites and information on your use of the Site itself, such as the domain name, Internet Service Provider, browser type and version, pages viewed, information accessed, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address you use to connect to the Internet. We also collect information in relation to Cookies – for more information, please review our policy on cookies.

_Demographic Information_. We collect and store demographic information (your post code, gender and age). We may also collect and store demographic information (such as your zip code, gender and age), and use this data to tailor your experience on our Websites, ensure you are at least 18 years of age to make purchases, provide content that we think you might be interested in, perform general improvements to the Websites, and display the content according to your preferences. Such demographic information may be shared with partners, market researchers and other third parties on an aggregate, non-personally identifiable basis. _No personally identifiable information_ will be linked to such aggregated demographic information that is shared with third parties

_Telephone Recording and Monitoring_. To ensure 1AutomationWiz.com customers receive quality service, 1AutomationWiz.com selects phone calls for recording and/or monitoring. These calls, between 1AutomationWiz.com customers (or potential customers) and team members, are evaluated by supervisors and/or other 1AutomationWiz.com representatives. This is to guarantee that prompt, consistent assistance and accurate information is delivered in a professional manner.

**Information we receive from other sources** :

We may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other services we provide. In this case we will have informed you when we collected that data that it may be shared internally and combined with data collected on this Site. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers, credit reference agencies) and may receive information about you from them.

**EU-U.S. Privacy Shield**

Web.com Group and it's subsidiaries and partner sites, participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Web.com Group Inc, and it's associated partners (1AutomationWiz.com) are committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List available at: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>

As the data collection, storage and processor of customer data for and through the 1AutomationWiz software, Web.com Group, Inc, is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. As such 1AutomationWiz complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Web.com Group, Inc is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. Additionally, Web.com Group and it's associated partners commits to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the advice given by such authorities with regard to human resources data transferred from the EU and Switzerland in the context of an employment relationship.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at: https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website at: https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint , you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

**Cookies** :

We use cookies on our Site to distinguish you from other users of our Site. This helps us to provide users with a good user experience when visiting our Site and also allows us to improve the Site. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the Site.

We use persistent cookies and session cookies on our Site. We use persistent cookies to save your login information for future log ins to the Site. We use session cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by users and web traffic routing on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site and then close your browser.

You can set up your browser options, to stop your computer accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use the whole of the Site or all functionality of the services. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set, how to manage and delete them, visit: [https://www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). To opt out of being tracked by google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout or by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page.

**How we use the personal data you give us**

To perform our contract with you. We use this information to perform our contract with you and fulfil your requests, such as:  

• Sending you requested service information;  
• Fulfilling your order;  
• Billing for services;  
• Creating directories (only when you explicitly ask to be included)  
• Responding to customer service requests, questions and concerns; and  
• Administering your account.

* Note that, generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are transactional and not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to cancel your services with us.  

We also engage other companies, individuals, and affiliates of 1AutomationWiz.com to perform certain functions and services for you. These third parties:  

• process credit card payments;  
• provide marketing assistance; and  
• remove duplicate information from customer lists.  

To contact you. If you have given your consent to send you e-mail, phone or SMS marketing, or if you have provided us with your postal address, we will use the personal data you give to us to contact you from time to time. If you register on the Site, you can choose to provide your consent to receive marketing communications by e-mail, phone and/or cell number (including use of automated dialling equipment and/or pre-recorded calls), text (SMS) message, social networks or any other means of communication that your device may be capable of receiving (i.e. video, etc.). If you do not want to receive postal or electronic communications, you may withdraw your consent at any time, by clicking the link in a communication, or emailing us using the address provided below.  

*For services in the United States, by registering on a Website and providing your telephone number, you agree that this action constitutes a purchase, inquiry and/or application for purposes.

To protect our Site and our business. We monitor use of the Sites and we use the information we collect, including personal data, to pursue our legitimate interest in protecting you, others and the Site itself by:  

• identifying fraudulent activities and transactions;  
• preventing abuse of the Sites and investigating and/or seeking prosecution for any potential threats to or misuse of the Sites;  
• ensuring compliance with the applicable terms of service and this Privacy Policy;  
• investigating violations of or enforcing these agreements; and  
• otherwise protecting the rights and property of 1AutomationWiz.com, its partners, and customers.  

To improve our services.

In order to pursue our legitimate interest in improving our Sites, we also use personal data to conduct research and analysis and to identify what services you and other customers like you need:  

• to better understand how people interact with our websites to provide communications about products which we think will be of interest to you; and to determine the effectiveness of promotional campaigns and advertising.  

Whenever we process data for these purposes we will ensure that we always keep your personal data rights in high regard and take account of these rights. You have the right to object to this processing if you wish and if you wish to do so, please click here to update your communication preferences. Please bear in mind that if you object this may affect our ability to carry out tasks above for your benefit.

Please note you always have the ability to opt-out of receiving future marketing communications from us. To opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us, you should follow the directions in the marketing e-mail or direct mail marketing communication from us. Please note that even though you may have opted out of receiving marketing communications, you may still receive business-related communications such as order confirmations, product recall information or updates or other organizational related communications.

**Information we collect about you:**

We will use this information to:

  1. administer our Site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
  2. improve our Site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer;
  3. allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  4. take measures to keep our Site safe and secure;
  5. measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
  6. make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our Site about goods or services that may interest you or them.

**Information we receive from other sources:**

We may combine this information with personal data you give to us and personal data we collect about you. We may use this personal data and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).

**Disclosure of your personal data** :

We may provide your personal data to companies that help us with our business activities (e.g. assisting us in Site operations, providing customer service, etc.) or that assist us in improving our products, content, services or advertising. These companies are authorized to use your personal data only as necessary to provide these services.

We will also share your personal data:

• As required by law, court order or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency (including ICANN) in order to enforce or apply our Services Agreement or other agreements.

• When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government request. This includes exchanging information with law enforcement, other companies and organizations for fraud protection, credit risk reduction or other similar purposes.

• In connection with a corporate change including a merger, acquisition, transfer or sale of assets or in connection to insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership. Information about our users, including customer information, will also need to be disclosed to our legal and financial advisors, investors or potential buyer in some commercial transactions seeking financing, investment or support or funding.

• To any other third party where we have your prior informed consent to do so.

• To other entities belonging to 1AutomationWiz.com (i.e. any companies directly or indirectly controlled by 1AutomationWiz.com).

**Where we transfer your personal data** :  

Our Sites are operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States.

Because 1AutomationWiz is a private label partner of Web.com’s shopping cart technology, Web.com handles and secures all personal customer data originating from interaction with our site and use of the 1AutomationWiz.com software platform. As such, Web.com participates in and complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce with respect to the collection, use and retention of personal information that is transferred from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland to the United States (collectively, the “Framework”). To learn more about the Privacy Shield program and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/. To provide adequate protection for certain EU Personal Data and Swiss Personal Data about corporate customers, clients, suppliers, and business partners received in the U.S., the party responsible for securing all user data for the 1AutomationWiz system, Web.com has elected to self-certify to the Framework administered by the U.S. Department of Commerce (“Privacy Shield”). Web.com adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement, and Liability. Web.com is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives from interaction with the 1AutomationWiz software platform under the Privacy Shield Framework, and for any subsequent transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Web.com complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions. For purposes of enforcing compliance with the Privacy Shield, Web.com is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the United States Federal Trade Commission with regard to our compliance with the Privacy Shield. 1AutomationWiz.com and or Web.com may be required to disclose personal information to law enforcement, regulatory or other government agencies, or to other third parties, in each case to comply with legal, regulatory, or national security obligations or requests. 1AutomationWiz.com and Web.com commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact 1AutomationWiz.com by e-mail at privacyshield@web.com.

We will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints or disputes within 45 days of receiving your complaint. Web.com’s independent recourse mechanism for Privacy Shield complaints for use by EU and Swiss individuals is JAMS. If you are unsatisfied with the resolution of your complaint, you may contact JAMS at https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield for further information and assistance. You may have the option to select binding arbitration for the resolution of your complaint under certain circumstances, provided you have taken the following steps: (1) raised your complaint directly with Web.com and provided us the opportunity to resolve the issue; (2) made use of the independent dispute resolution mechanism identified above; and (3) raised the issue through the relevant data protection authority and allowed the US Department of Commerce an opportunity to resolve the complaint at no cost to you. If you have any questions about this 1AutomationWiz.com participation in the Privacy Shield Framework please contact us as follows: privacyshield@web.com or by mail at Web.com, Inc., Attn.: Privacy Officer, 12808 Gran Bay Parkway West, Jacksonville, FL 32258.

**Protection of personal data** :

We have implemented technical, physical and administrative security measures to help protect against the loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access of personal data that we may collect from you, or that you provide to us. Our Site is scanned on a regular basis for known vulnerabilities including regular malware scanning. Your personal data is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have authorised access to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

We have taken numerous steps to ensure that personal data is processed confidentially, accurately and securely. The Site use encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal data during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address and credit card number. Additionally, all financial transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is completely secure and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. And although we will endeavour to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site. Any transmission is at your own risk. You can further help to ensure your security by taking a few simple precautions. For instance, it is important to protect against unauthorized access to your computer and to any 1AutomationWiz.com user name and password, and to be sure to sign off when you are finished using a shared computer.

**Passwords** :

When you create an online account on the Site, you need to select a personal password. To maximise your level of protection, you should choose at least 8-30 characters including a combination of numbers, letters and varying case. You are solely responsible for keeping your password or any account information confidential We ask you not to share any password with anyone.

**Security breach notification** :

We shall give notice to each Organization Administrator when the organization’s user personal data was, or it is reasonably believed to have been, inappropriately accessed as a result of a security breach. Said notice shall be made immediately upon confirmed discovery of the breach and the time necessary such as to allow us to determine the scope of the breach, to identify organizations and individuals affected by the breach, and to restore reasonable integrity of the data system that was breached.

If a federal, state, or local law enforcement agency determines that notice to organizations required under this policy would interfere with a criminal investigation, the notice shall be delayed upon the written request of the law enforcement agency for a specified period that the law enforcement agency determines is reasonably necessary. A law enforcement agency may, by a subsequent written request, revoke such delay as of a specified date or extend the period set forth in the original request made under this paragraph to a specified date if further delay is necessary. Notice to the affected organizations is not required if, after an appropriate investigation and consultation with relevant federal, state, or local law enforcement that it is reasonable to believe no user personal data was accessed by unauthorized individuals.

**Links to other Websites** :

Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, subsidiaries and group companies, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Your rights in relation to your personal data** :

You will be entitled to ask us:  
• For access to a copy of your personal data  
• To correct, erase or restrict our processing of your personal data  
• To transfer the information you have provided under contract or consent to another organization  
• To stop processing your information, by withdrawing your consent or objecting to our legitimate interests.

Your rights in relation to your personal data are limited in some situations. For example, if we have a legal requirement or a compelling legitimate ground we may continue to process your information. We will provide you with information on whether there are limits or exemptions that apply to any request that you make.

In the first instance you can view or change the information you have provided us with by submitting a request via e-mail or logging in to your online account manager, if applicable.  

You can make a request in relation to any of the above rights by writing to us at the contact address given at the end of this Privacy Policy. We will respond to such queries within 30 days and deal with requests we receive from you, in accordance with the provisions of the Act.

Please note, however, that no financial information will be provided over the phone, and in no event will such information be provided without verification. You also have the right to make a complaint if you feel your personal data has been mishandled. We encourage you to come to us in the first instance but, to the extent that this right applies to you, you are entitled to complain directly to the relevant supervisory authority. This can be the supervisory authority where you reside or work, or where you believe a breach has taken place.

**Consent** :

You have the right to withdraw your consent to us processing your personal data, at any time, by writing to us at the contact address given at the end of this Privacy Policy. Where we process your personal data for marketing purposes, we will inform you and obtain your opt in consent (before collecting your personal data). If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please click on the opt out options and we will remove you from our mailing lists.

**Data retention** :

We keep information only for as long as we need it to provide you services, manage our business or as required by law or contract. Where you have a contract with us, we will retain your data for the length of the contract, and will further retain that information for a time period consistent with our legal or regulatory responsibilities, after you terminate all your services with us to resolve disputes, enforce our relevant Service Agreement, and to adhere to the technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of the Sites. If you have any questions about how long we will keep your specific data, please contact privacy@ web.com.

**Complaints** :

If you have any complaints about our use of your personal data please contact us as set out at the end of this Privacy Policy or contact the supervisory authority of the country in which you reside.

**Children** :

You must be at least eighteen years old to register online or purchase our goods or services. 1AutomationWiz.com does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of eighteen.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy** :

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time, and will communicate changes to this Policy via e-mail to users who have provided an e-mail address and post a notice on our Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review the current Privacy Policy made available on our Site for the latest information on our privacy practices. This Privacy Policy was last updated on April 25th, 2018 and replaces any other Privacy Policy previously applicable from this date.

**Contact** :

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to:

By telephone at any of the following numbers:  
1-800-360-3189  
1-800-671-3871  
By e-mail: privacy@1shoppingcart.com  
By post: 1 ShoppingCart  
Privacy Officer  
12808 Gran Bay Parkway West  
Jacksonville, FL 32258  
Phone: 904-680-6600

**Privacy Policy Updates** :

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any substantial changes in the way we use your Personal Information, we will post an alert on this page. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our website, products and services. Continued use of our website, products or services following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgment of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

**Conditions of Use and Revisions** :

If you choose to visit 1AutomationWiz’s website, or use our products or services, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy, as governed by the laws of the State of Florida.

Back
